Tushar Pal

Desinger and Developer

I am a 22-year old B.Tech graduate with Electronics and Communication Engineering background. I have skills in both Tech and Creative fields and currently working as a Freelancer. I have experience of almost 4 years in working as a Graphic Designer and an Art Director in a startup company.



tushar.pal9932@gmail.com

7063028090

Vill-Bhaluka, Post-Tiluri, Bankura, India

tusharpal0411.github.io/Tushar-Portfolio/

W

linkedin.com/in/Tushar Pal

instagram.com/@tusharrt

EDUCATION

B.Tech

Asansol Engineering College

06/2019 - 07/2023

Asansol, WB, India

Courses

 Electronics & Communications Engineering

Higher Secondary

Santaldih Thermal Power Station High School (H.S.)

06/2017 - 04/2019

Santaldih, Purulia, WB

Secondary

Tiluri Kripamoyee High School

02/2016 - 04/2017

Tiluri, Bankura, WB

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Designer

(Web / Graphic / UI & UX)

04/2024 - Present

Creative/Art Director

Small Town Talks (NASSCOM)

04/2022 - 03/2024 Asansol, India Small Town Talks is a Digital Marketing Company specialised in digital strategies to gain traffic for any organization or business.

Achievements/Tasks

• Lead of the department of Art in this company.

Graphic Designer

Small Town Talks (NASSCOM)

07/2020 - 03/2022

Asansol, India

ACHIEVEMENTS

Visharad Degree (Masters) in Fine Arts From -Sarbabharatiya Sangeet-O-Sanskriti Parishad (2019)

SKILLS

Frontend Web Development

Graphic Designing

UI Designing

UX Designing

Digital Illustration

HTML

CSS

MySQL

C++

Java

LEARNINGS

Javascript

Figma

Java

CERTIFICATES

 Coursera - Programming Foundations with JavaScript, HTML and CSS

https://coursera.org/share/becfc323cd6ef7387df9a4271e25d627

• UI/UX for Beginners by Great Learning (04/2024) https://www.linkedin.com/posts/tushar-pal-03687b1a3_1000-free-courses-with-free-certificates-activity-7191101376054099970-GVBN2 utm_source=share&utm_medium=member_desktop

Digital Skills: User Experience by Accenture (05/2024)

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/r6wlgnd

PERSONAL PROJECTS

• Website for a Social Club using HTML and CSS (05/2022)

It's a website of a social club that is located in my village. The website contains the description of the club, all the past and upcoming events of the club, a photo gallery with description, contact details (like email, social media handles), a notice board and a membership request form.

 Portfolio website for a Photographer using HTML and CSS (10/2023)

It's a portfolio website of a photographer that contains his where-abouts, a photo gallery that is his woks(photographs) with description, his contact details like his social media handles, email and whatsapp.

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Bengali

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Painting

Photography

Writing Poems and Stories